childstarlets.com 2019-04-13

# CHILDSTARLETS.COM - Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy

Updated December 2015

Childstarlets.com is committed to protecting your privacy. This privacy policy explains about how we handle visitor and member data.  

**Visitors to our website (non-members):**  
You may browse the site freely except for specific member-supported areas. As you browse the site, certain kinds of information, such as the website that referred you to us, your IP address, browser type and language, and access times, may be collected automatically by the web hosting software. This is a normal function of every website. 

If a visitor contacts us via e-mail, using our contact page, or in any other way, we do require an e-mail address to reply to. We only use that e-mail address for the purpose intended (to reply to your inquiry). We never collect, sell, or share this e-mail address with anyone else.   

**Members of our site:**  
The data gathered from your visit is treated the same as non-member visitors (above), with the following additions/exceptions: 

When you sign up as a member of our site, we ask for some personal information such as your name and e-mail address. We never share this information with anyone else other than our payment processors (their privacy policies also apply). We may correspond directly with you concerning your current or expired membership, but we do not share or sell our members' e-mail addresses to any organization public or private.

Signing up as a member involves providing our payment processors with billing information such as credit/debit card numbers or checking account data. We do not have access to any of this information. This data is safeguarded by SSL connections to our payment processors and is subject to their privacy and security policies. 

To protect our content from misuse, or In cases of violations of our terms of service (sharing of logins, posting our content on other websites, etc.) we may gather browsing data related to your logins to our site. We may use cookies to assist in this process.   

**Other Policies:  
**While browsing our site, you will find links to other websites such as fansites, payment processors, and commercial advertisers. Once you leave Childstarlets.com, you are no longer covered by our privacy policy. You should refer to the privacy policies of these other sites while you are there. We assume no responsibility for the policies or practices of such linked sites, and encourage you to become acquainted with them prior to use.

By using this site, you understand and agree to the terms of this policy.   
We reserve the right to change the terms of this privacy policy at any time. When we make changes, we will revise the "last updated" date at the top of the policy.
